Ming Shun Kwek

Software Student

Currently a year 3 computer engineering student studying at National University of Singapore. Clear communicator and determine in tasks I set my mind too. Forward-thinking development professional bringing expertise in Java, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and other programming languages. Diligently learning everything I can, gaining more experience in different fields so that one day, I could contribute more towards the world of technology.

Work History

2021-06 -2022-02

Java Software Developer

Integro Technologies Pte Ltd

- Troubleshot various software issues by using debugging processes and coding techniques.
- Investigated issues and defects to determine problem root cause and formulate corrective action recommendations, successfully resolving over 30 issues.
- Wrote, modified and maintained software documentation and specifications.

2019-11 -2020-08

Head of Programmes

NUS Raffles Hall Freshmen Orientation Camp

- Coordinated sequence of programmes for 200
 freshmen, while maintaining communication across
 multiple departments to ensure smooth operation
 while clarifying conflicting ideas.
- Spearheading team of 10, like-minded individuals while resolve conflicting visions, guiding innovation towards enhancing event flow.

2020-05 -2020-07

Software Development

NUS Orbital Programme

 Developed SmartTrack savings application in React Native that aids in budget management with additional features that ease expense sharing with

Contact

Address

Singapore, Singapore

Phone

(+65) 8125 9299

E-mail

mingshun1998@hotmail.co m

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/kwekming-shun

GitHub

https://github.com/MingSh un98

Personal Website

https://mingshun98.github.i o/Portfolio-Website/

Skills

Object-Oriented Programming



Effective Communication for Computing Professionals



Data Structures and Algorithms



Code versioning

other users.

- Achieved Apollo 11 (advanced) standard certification, determined to have demonstrated awareness of basics in software engineering, testing and documentation.
- Picked up relevant software development skills and knowledge like Javascript and Google Firebase API.

2018-11 - Contracts/Projects Assistant

YL Integrated PTE LTD

- Analyzed and calculated required lighting and fire emergency equipment in floor plans for tender projects, necessary for purchase and installation.
- Managed contact between suppliers and company, answering inquires regarding quotations as well as purchase orders.
- Managed and mentored team of 3 employees, overseeing training, and professional growth of employees.

2017-08 - Sergeant, 1st Battalion Singapore Guards

Singapore Armed Forces (National Service)

- Planned for mission objectives and engaging in discussions with full time servicemen to better optimized battle plans and efficient routes for mission success.
- Facilitated 30+ recruits as an instructor, teaching and mentoring enlistees, later transitioned into leader role after recruits graduated from Basic Training and thereafter, being responsible for them during active service.

Education

2019-06

2018-11

2019-08 - Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Engineering

Current National University of Singapore

• GPA: 4.05/5.00

2015-01 - High School Diploma 2016-12 Nanyana Junior Colle

Nanyang Junior College

 Achieved 78.75 RP with 2 H2 Distinctions in Chemistry and Mathematics.



Functional Specification documentation



Mobile/ Web Development



Languages

English



Mandarin Chinese



Software

Java Programming



C++ Programming



HTML/ CSS / JavaScript



C Programming



Git/ Github



Python



SQL

